wineawesomeness.com 2017-11-19

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of Wine Awesomeness, Inc, doing business as Wine Awesomeness ("we", "our" or "us") on the collection, use and disclosure of your information on WineAwesomeness.com (the "Site") and the services, features, content or applications we offer (collectively with the Site, the "Services"). We receive information about you from various sources, including: (i) if you register for the Site and the Services, through your user account on the Services (your "Account"); (ii) your use of the Services generally; and (iii) from third party websites and services. When you use the Services, you are consenting to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. The Services are not available to individuals under 21 years of age.

This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") gathered when you are using or accessing the Services. This Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of any Personal Information that our business partners share with us or that we share with our business partners.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third party websites, services and applications ("Third Party Services") that you elect to access through the Service or to individuals that we do not manage or employ. While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Services. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any Third Party Services you access.

### What Information Do We Collect?

In connection with certain aspects of the Services, we collect some of your Personal Information. One goal in collecting Personal Information from you is to provide an efficient, meaningful, and customized experience. For example, we can use your Personal Information to:

-help make this Site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once;  
-help you quickly find information, products, and services;  
-help us create content on this Site that is most relevant to you;  
-alert you to new information, products, and services that we offer; and  
-deliver you the most awesome box possible. 

### We also may collect the following information:

-name  
-contact information including email address  
-demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests  
-other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offer.

### User Content

Some features of the Services allow you to provide content to the Services, such as written comments. All content submitted by you to the Services may be retained by us indefinitely, even after you terminate your Account. We may continue to disclose such content to third parties in a manner that does not reveal Personal Information, as described in this Privacy Policy.

### User Supplied Information

Some features of the Services may give you the option to request information, complete surveys or otherwise interact with us and our partners. We may collect information you provide in connection with your profile such as, but not limited to, your likes, dislikes, profession, hobbies, gender, age, and location. Information that you supply in connection with the Services is solely at your discretion. If you do supply Personal Information in response to such requests, we may use it for the purposes stated in that feature of the Services.

### Financial and Account Information

When you create an Account, you will provide information that could be Personal Information, such as your username, password, email address, shipping and billing address(es), mobile phone number, and credit card number. This type of Personal Information is used for billing purposes, to fulfill your orders, to communicate with you about your order and our site, and for internal marketing purposes. If we encounter a problem when processing your order, we use the Personal Information to contact you. We do not currently store financial information, such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information); that information is stored by our third party payment processing company (the "Payment Processor"), and use and storage of that information is governed by the Payment Processor's applicable terms of service and privacy policy.

###   
Email Communications

You may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. As part of the Services, you will also receive emails and other communications from us relating to your Account, your subscription, and deliveries you have ordered. We may also occasionally send you marketing emails about the Services that we offer. We will never sell your email address to a third party without your permission.

###   
Is Information About Me Secure?

Your Account information will be protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your Account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your Account.

We seek to protect Account information to ensure that it is kept private; however, we cannot guarantee the security of any Account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

We otherwise store all of our information, including your IP address information, using industry-standard techniques. We do not guarantee or warrant that such techniques will prevent unauthorized access to information about you that we store, Personal Information or otherwise.

### What we do with the information we gather?

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

-Internal record keeping.  
-We may use the information to improve our products and services.  
-We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.  
-From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

-whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes

-if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@wineawesomeness.com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to support@wineawesomeness.com twitter: @wineawesomeness Chat Support Available M-F 10-5.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
